{
    "subject": "resource/Jean_Dieudonn\u00e9",
    "predicate": "ontology/doctoralStudent",
    "object": "resource/Kishore_Marathe",
    "human_readable": "Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 was a doctoral student of Kishore Marathe.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9100461602210999,
            "question": "Who guided Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 through his doctoral studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8802114725112915,
            "question": "Are there any other potential connections between Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 and Kishore Marathe beyond their student-advisor relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8765389323234558,
            "question": "Who was Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's doctoral advisor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8748654723167419,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 and Kishore Marathe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8632954359054565,
            "question": "How might the work of Kishore Marathe have influenced Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7642872333526611,
            "question": "Was Kishore Marathe a professor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5594845414161682,
            "question": "Can you infer anything about Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's academic path from this information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.400389701128006,
            "question": "To what field of study is Kishore Marathe likely associated based on this relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2605043947696686,
            "question": "What other prominent mathematicians have potentially been associated with Kishore Marathe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08760472387075424,
            "question": "What kind of educational institution might have facilitated this doctoral relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 was a doctoral student of Kishore Marathe.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7013_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other prominent mathematicians have potentially been associated with Kishore Marathe?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7013_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what field of study is Kishore Marathe likely associated based on this relationship?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7013_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you infer anything about Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's academic path from this information?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7013_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7013_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7013_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7013_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7013_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7013_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7013_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7013_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7013_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7013_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7013_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide any information supporting that Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 was a doctoral student of Kishore Marathe. On the contrary, it mentions that Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 supervised the PhD of Grothendieck."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 was a French mathematician who lived from 1906 to 1992, and there is no evidence or mention in the provided context that he was ever a doctoral student of Kishore Marathe.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Kishore Marathe as a person or figure related to Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's academic journey or life.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information about Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 being a doctoral student of Kishore Marathe in the provided context.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 was a specialist in group theory, topology, and functional analysis, and the context information mentions that he was a PhD advisor to Grothendieck. There is no mention of his being a doctoral student of Kishore Marathe, which contradicts the given claim.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}